tenmarks.com 2012-06-30

# TenMarks | Privacy Policy

TenMarks - Privacy Policy 

TenMarks is the smartest way for kids to practice and master math. It's an ideal supplemental education resource that can be used by parents or educators to support and enhance their students learning. TenMarks is very effective and super easy. 

TenMarks Education, Inc. (TenMarks) feels strongly about protecting your privacy and the privacy of a child.

TenMarks WILL NOT sell, trade, or assign any unaggregated, personally-identifiable personal information that it collects to third parties outside of TenMarks. If you have any questions, concerns or comments regarding this privacy policy, you may contact us at the email and address posted at the end of this policy statement. We are committed to addressing your privacy or security questions or concerns. 

1\. Information Collected by TenMarks

In order for you to participate in the TenMarks Beta Program, the TenMarks Free Trial Program, and/or other TenMarks products (the "Programs"), you and/or your child must register on TenMarks. This registration process will require you/your child to provide their name, email addresses, phone number, school and grade level information of the child, and, if payment will be required for the Programs, your credit card information, including billing address. We call this information "Registration Information." 

2\. How TenMarks will use the information collected from you

Mailing Address: Your mailing address may be used to allow TenMarks to mail you various Program materials and ancillary program products. 

Email Address: Email addresses will serve as the login username for you and your child. The email addresses may be used to send a confirmation email at registration, as well as information and updates to the Programs. We will also email reports, with further information about the progress a child is making on the Programs. We may use the email addresses as an additional means of communicating with you and your child about the Programs and TenMarks, including notifying you of updates to the Web Site or its related policies. 

Credit Card Information: With your consent, we may use and save your credit card information to bill them for each child that are registered and linked to them for the Programs. 

Phone Number: Your phone number will serve as an alternate way of contacting you for the same purposes as the email address. 

Child's Name: A child's name will be used to customize a child's participation in the Programs, as well as to personalize the reports and updates about the child's progress in the Programs. In addition, we may mail related material to the child using his/her name, at the mailing address that is provided. 

Relationship to Child: A parent/teacher's relationship to the Child will be used for profile and tracking purposes and to personalize the child's reports. 

Child's School Grade Level: We will use a child's grade level to group Performance Data of children of similar grade levels so we can assess performance by grade level, and improve the program. 

Secondary Uses: Registration Information and other information may be used by us for demographic profiling and targeted advertising, although in such cases, the information will be aggregated as ANONYMOUS statistical information. 

Participation History: The details of any order you place and the Programs you or a child choose will be collected for customer service, marketing and business purposes. 

3\. Information TenMarks collects directly from a child

TenMarks collects information directly from a child, over the Internet, in the form of the interactions that a child makes when participating in the Programs. We refer to the data resulting from such participation, which includes but is not limited to data on when a child starts and stops a lesson, the responses a child makes to questions asked, the timing of a child's responses, a child's choice of character and customizations, and the choice of lessons to play as "Performance Data." We will use Performance Data to (1) measure a child's performance in each lesson of the TenMarks Programs and to adapt the Programs to his or her education needs, (2) analyze a child's Performance Data, and provide the child and the associated parent/school official with periodic progress reports about a child's performance in the Programs, and (3) improve the Programs. If we ever need to collect information that is not Performance Data directly from a child, TenMarks will seek your authorization prior to collecting such additional information from a child. In addition, we may aggregate a child's Performance Data with the Performance Data of other children participating in the Programs for marketing and other business related purposes. Aggregate information will be ANONYMOUS and will not identify a child. 

4\. Opting-out of providing the information we request

Because the TenMarks Programs are individualized and customized for each child, all the information we request from you and a child is required for you and a child to participate in the Programs, with the exception of certain information to be used for our marketing purposes to you only. At any time, you may revoke your consent to allowing a child to participate in the TenMarks Programs or refuse to allow TenMarks to further use or collect a child's personal information. Any ANONYMOUS performance data will be retained, but we will no longer use any identifiable information regarding you or a child that you have provided. However, if you do any of the foregoing, you and a child will not be able to participate in the Programs. 

5\. Reviewing and changing your information

You may review and modify your Registration Information at any time by accessing our website using your password, and sending us a support mail with a request to change it. 

6\. Consent

In order to use the Programs, you and/or your child are asked to submit certain personal information about yourselves and to authorize TenMarks to use that information in a limited number of ways. We ask you and/or the child to ensure that the Parent has reviewed and submitted a Parental Consent as part of the registration process, which will require you to consent to our collection and use of information directly from a child over the Internet as described above. 

7\. Password Protection

You and your child will be asked to select a password each to access the Programs through our website, and this password will be used to allow you and the child to use the Programs. The passwords should be kept confidential. Your password will also allow you to review and change the information we collect about you and a child or children. 

8\. Protecting your information.

No data transmissions over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. Consequently, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us and you do so at your own risk. TenMarks has multiple security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of information under our control. 

Please note that this Program is hosted in North America. If you are visiting from the European Union or other regions with laws governing data collection and use that may differ from U.S./Canadian laws, please note that you are transferring your personal data to the United States/Canada, which does not have the same data protection laws as the EU or other regions and by providing your personal data you consent to the use of your personal data for the uses identified above in accordance with this Privacy Policy; and the transfer of your personal data to the United States/Canada as indicated above. 

9\. Your information and third parties

Except as provided in this Privacy Policy, TenMarks WILL NOT disclose the information that it obtains from you to third parties without your express written permission, or where we believe, in good faith, that the law requires us to disclose the information. 

TenMarks WILL NOT sell, trade, or assign any unaggregated personal information that it collects to third parties outside of TenMarks. We, however, may aggregate the information that we collect from users of our website to create demographic profiles and performance profiles regarding the progress of children who use the Programs. TenMarks may share aggregated information with marketing professionals, or potential investors. This aggregated information will be compiled and reported in the form of ANONYMOUS group statistics only. 

Notwithstanding anything to the contrary, as TenMarks continues to develop its business, it might sell some or all of its assets. In such transactions, customer information is generally one of the transferred business assets. An acquiring company would be required to protect all information that TenMarks collects from users of our website and Programs in accordance with the terms of this Privacy Policy. 

10\. Unsolicited third-party promotional emails

TenMarks will not send you unsolicited third-party promotional emails. 

11\. Use of cookies

As a standard practice, TenMarks uses "cookies". A cookie is a small amount of data sent to your browser from our web server and stored on your computer, then sent back to the server by your browser each time you access our website. Cookies enable us to track usage of our website. In addition, cookies are required for the operation of the Programs. Please note that if you refuse the TenMarks cookie (by turning cookies off in your browser or by clicking "don't accept" if you have set your browser to warn you before accepting cookies), our Programs will not work. Cookies cannot be used to gather personal information from your computer. 

12\. Children's Online Privacy Protection Act

Congress has enacted a law called the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 (COPPA) which is designed to protect children's privacy during use of the Internet. TenMarks has implemented practices consistent with the guidelines provided by the Federal Trade Commission to date. 

TenMarks will never knowingly request personally identifiable information or private content from anyone under the age of 13 without parental consent. TENMARKS DOES NOT SHARE CHILDREN'S PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION WITH THIRD PARTIES. If you are a parent or legal guardian of a user under 13 you may, at any time, revoke your consent to allow a child to use the Programs under your subscription, refuse to allow TenMarks to further use or collect a child's personal information, or direct TenMarks to delete all identifiable information regarding a child that you have provided. To do so, please contact our Privacy Officer at the contact information below. However, if you do any of the foregoing, a child will not be able to use the Programs. 

If you would like more information about COPPA, please go to  
<http://www.ftc.gov/ogc/coppa1.htm>

13\. The Children's Internet Protection Act

The Children's Internet Protection Act (CIPA) is a federal law enacted by Congress in December 2000 to address concerns about access to offensive content over the Internet on school and library computers. CIPA imposes certain types of requirements on any school or library that receives funding support for Internet access or internal connections from the "E-rate" program - a program that makes certain technology more affordable for eligible schools and libraries. Our Programs do not provide links to external resources or chat rooms, and do not contain any offensive or inappropriate matter. As a result, any school or library that uses TenMarks Programs will be fully compliant with CIPA. If you would like more information about CIPA, please go to [http://www.fcc.gov/cgb/consumerfacts/cipa.html.](http://www.fcc.gov/cgb/consumerfacts/cipa.html)

14\. The Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act

The Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act (FERPA) is a Federal law that protects the privacy of student education records. The law applies to all schools that receive funds under an applicable program of the U.S. Department of Education. 

FERPA gives parents certain rights with respect to their children's education records. These rights transfer to the student when he or she reaches the age of 18 or attends a school beyond the high school level. 

TenMarks is fully compliant with FERPA. Specifically: 

  * Any sensitive online information is transmitted over secure channels.
  * All student data are stored in ways that are not publicly accessible.
  * Security audits are regularly performed to ensure data integrity.

TenMarks does not share student information with any third parties. If a school requests that student data should be sent to a third party, with parental consent, TenMarks would send the data to the school and never directly to the third party. 

If you would like more information about FERPA, please go to [http://www.ed.gov/policy/gen/guid/fpco/ferpa/index.html.](http://www.ed.gov/policy/gen/guid/fpco/ferpa/index.html)

15\. Amendments

TenMarks may amend this Privacy Policy from time to time. We may notify you by email regarding any material changes to our privacy and security practices. Please review all revisions to the Privacy Policy. Your continued use of our website(s) and the Programs after the date TenMarks has updates such policies will be deemed to be your agreement to the changed terms. 

16\. Contact Us

contact:  
The Privacy Officer  
TenMarks, Education Inc.  
46, Glen Avenue  
Newton MA 02459 Or email us at: [privacy@TenMarks.com](mailto:privacy@tenmarks.com)
